Only seven days, 13 hours, and 23 minutes until Valentine's Day.
What's our plan this year?
Oh, you're right.
We all should put together some ideas then.
First off, we gotta be real nice to the younger girls.
And make it obvious we like sweet stuff.
Then we gotta make sure we walk the halls near their classes day up.
That's a plan to get chocolates!
Valentine's Day.
Never been interested.
Hey, why don't we all make some ourselves to dish out to the boys?
Oh!
That seems fun!
You know there won't be a single boy alive who says no if we tell him I wanna help us make them.
Right, little E.T.?
Hey, hang on now!
Wouldn't that count as me giving all the boys chocolates and not just the ones I choose to?
Wanna call it off then?
Um, I don't really know.
That's hard to decide.
I've always wanted you to show me how to make snacks and stuff.
And we all know chocolate is the king of snacks!
Exactly!
Which means all the more reason for us to do a little chocolate run.
So meet at my place then?
Huh?
Oh, um...
Let's do it at mine!
What?
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Huh?
Yeah!
Mm-hmm.
Wait.
Why am I a part of this?
Who's there?
We'll go over the table.
We'll keep you back on it.
Everyone's good.
Yeah!
Why am I a part of this?
We'll keep you back once again!
Oh, we've got to show that everybody's Joe J.T.
Let's do it anyway!
took it to respect each other.
It took it from the end of the day.
For us, what's your day?
A lot of times more, we'll be
going to spend our time on Instagram, and you can obviously wake up and do top dice.
Okay, stand it.
Alright guys!
Fire-me will be able to.
Awesome.
We'll keep you back on Instagram...
Never!
Let's do it at home across the top andilib意.
We'll keep you back.
back again why would you even invite me to this though they're making chocolate for all the guys
huh oh ichikawa uh hey what are the odds so what are you doing around here uh huh
we're about to head into yamada's place to make some chocolate goodies
i'm just passing by what wait what's going on was i not actually invited let's do it at mine
okay i guess she really didn't actually invite me i want to die more than i have for half a decade
the rest of them are yamada's friends to them i'm just a piece of trash that's in the same class
should have realized that from the start wait hang on though yesterday she
maybe this was a missed text or it meant something else what's up
i uh this is the place come on now we are going in
i have no idea what's going on he and i we're good friends now does she really think that
it's about time you came wait hang on you eating our ingredients uh no of course not this is something
else you sure are dressed up you really think so then come on in
careful what you do in there her mom's super strict about her girl
oh no wait what come on in thanks for having us over
a boy is here
so how is it you know my daughter
do i say we're friends are we what even is a friend oh don't worry about him he's like my bae
you what oh is that so you kids these days all right what choice was there really is that for
real is that why you brought him byashiko why not have your dad teach you because he says it's too
dangerous for him to teach me mm-hmm might have a point i still feel like i shouldn't have come
i'll do it uh oh dear
i'll get it oh you silly little boy my my hands don't you all of this is bad none of this can be
good okay all set all right then it's i mean kyotaro do me a favor pass that over uh this know that
the two of your classmates together isn't that right when did you start stop just leave us be
all right are you kids gonna be okay on your own so what are you thinking of doing for white day
you better start thinking hard and fast about it huh what's that supposed to mean nothing for you to
worry about by ashiko in fact don't even think about it honestly now everyone is growing up right
before my eyes the only kids left are me and yamada it seems i was thinking anna loves all sorts
of food and all right but what is it that she likes the very most even i can't answer that
i mean in fact ever since we first met each other last year i never really got her hi i'm anna
yamada from class one one honestly my first impression was she was huge miles away and never
made any sense like when i thought she hung back for extra practice
one two
is she seriously practicing spinning the ball she's crying just 80 seconds to go you weren't
even close that's just the way she's always been that's got nothing to do with what food she likes
yeah well if i had to guess what she really likes i'd say is me
serena can you pass me that oh yeah sure listen to me though for instance you should have heard
her after the ball thing the basketball tournament at my elementary school mm-hmm you got the most
points out of everyone right and like you're way smaller than sorry but still yeah yeah i can't believe
you still practice every day even though you're already that amazing she told me she looked up to
me and i was awesome so i doubt she went that far in saying that to you despite what you think
she's pretty mindful of folks around her think though what does she like what am i thinking the fact
she even invited me here probably means she doesn't think of me that sort of way i'm not sure i can
leave you kids to do this by yourselves sit here and be quiet and behave yourself then fine fine
ichi let's brainstorm ways how we're gonna do this huh what's that supposed to mean for starters
try calling me moiko what no way oh come on with it ichi give it a try moiko you're so bad at this
i can't stand it this isn't right
now what no need to yell at us so rudely like that pass me that back i'm gonna mix it in
what's with you
these are clearly some bad vibes
must be because i'm here having fun huh i guess oh
having fun
i'm just gonna use the bathroom
okay i'm leaving no you aren't huh first off her mom needs to know this isn't true otherwise
nothing good is going to come of this why's that let's say by some weird miracle you and yama to start
dating what are you going to say down the road when you meet that you broke up with seki ne to get with
yama to that would never happen so it doesn't matter anyway are you really okay with that
get off my back man i'm the one who'll get hurt if i hope at all i guess that's true
oh my are you leaving thanks for having me
miracles aren't real there was never any chance for me
but
the thing about me and second day dating wasn't true i'm sorry for lying my apologies
even still i want to believe in miracles in myself
is your name ichikawa by any chance huh yes i knew it your mother and i spoke before the last
parent teacher conference anna says the two of you are always talking to each other a little
while back she even told me she was mother get back inside
later then
stick around well uh okay
why didn't you deny it as soon as moeko lied
i mean if i did then your mom would ask what i was doing here with her daughter
i'd have forced you into lying to her all over again
i thought i should be the real me in front of her this time
i sound like such a creep let's head back in
i didn't think i still had it in me to actually think i stood a chance
i was like
no way this just won't do
definitely not
what is this thing
this is all too soon that's her dad right i can't read his face but i can tell
he's not happy i'm here
what was that just now he came out of nowhere should we have said or done something at least
michael
huh i'm sorry you were quick to help me back there but instead
we're way beyond that phase was that your father oh yeah he's a chef he cooks fancy french food
he's so big and tall like some kind of giant a giant
hang on that's the guy i saw in the elevator
there's no way he remembers me right i should be fine
what's wrong i shouldn't keep this to myself actually
i'm done with lies time for the truth games do you play huh um sure
what um what is going on
you pick who you want first
sorry about this he has no sense of personal space huh
it's just i'm the only one who plays games here
i play games as well
bow down before me
what is going on
you rocking some crazy pheromones no he's just a hardcore gamer although he doesn't really look
like anna does he you'd think a chef in a high rise like this would be more you know huh
perfect they're all done
can we ask mr yamada to test them out for us ma'am sure
he should just be in the other room he helped us out and all
did he now
so um here this is for you huh just a taste right
so go on try it
how is it
too sweet maybe
no i mean that's just my personal opinion
so this is why i'm glad you came
i'm exhausted even more than last time
hey ichikawa you've been over to her place before haven't you
i mean you knew where the bathroom was and hit the elevator button as soon as we got in
for real did you do really of course not i just had to stop by but you have been over huh
well anyway if you knew all that why'd you have to yell so loud and stuff you scared me
i get that you were trying to help the situation back there and all but you were clearly having fun
at it what you mean me girls are scary yamada seemed pretty upset that you were what
nah never mind
uh thanks for everything today don't mention it
i'm still headed this way though huh then why would you even stop don't get smart with us huh
if you do it say so or else not gonna happen aren't we friends you what you were making chocolates at
ana's house with everyone else yeah who else yamada's friends were they all girls yeah
you're already building up a harem come on what do you mean building one already
someone sure is busier than ever what is it i was just wondering what you thought of today
i mean about my mom and dad they both look like they're really strict i was honestly pretty scared
but once i started being straight with them they were real nice so i guess they were like i expected
them to be yeah you know what they said basically the same thing huh so dad what did you think of
today crowded not work i'm talking about my friends that came over today you brought over a boy
forgot to ask for his friend code i hope he comes back do you mean that
what about you mom let's see i guess they were like what i expected what do you think that means
it's me but stop asking them about me why because i'm a creature of the shadows hey get this about my
dad though he was calling you yamada for some odd reason told me to ask for yamada's friend code what
what are you drinking this is growing up oh hey want some amazake no i don't don't be like that
cheers
so hey i was thinking you gonna ask her out what a stereotypical reaction i'm sorry that was just
the drink talking but i figure you could give me a break i don't have the confidence
i have no idea how she feels or what my chances are no idea huh i'm not gonna try and force your hand or
anything weird like that you're still in junior high after all i figure you could take it slow for the
moment but you could also say since you're only in junior high you're gonna grow and find lots of
things you like and have fun with at the same time things around you will also change even your feelings
will change goes for you as much as anyone i mean do you know how many billions of women there are in
the world there's no telling when you'll have a change of heart i won't huh i think for me
i'll always like yamada if anything i'm positive about that but i can't tell her
but see yamada lives in a bigger world than i do one that's not familiar to someone like me
she's going to make mistakes but keep moving ahead
loving and being loved by so many people
if she suddenly had to go far away tomorrow i'm sure that she would forget about me in no time
i mean i wouldn't count on that i don't want her to
bro
you know it's never really about having a chance and all that it's about what you want to do
it starts from there i what i want to be her her boyfriend
i don't even care in the end never figured out what chocolate to give the guys in the end
there's no guarantee we have a tomorrow together and if there isn't then maybe i should maybe i can
or just don't
try for what i want a little